Hello Hello Friends, in today's video on
Health Technical Mau YouTube Hindi channel for all of you, we will
learn
how to make ICICI Lombard insurance from CSC, how to
subscribe and how to generate third party
policy first, we will give complete information about all these things
in this video,
so first of all what you have to do is
login to the digital seva portal, after logging in you have to log in like this,
please
click on the like and subscribe tab, thank you the
people, if you are visiting our channel for the first time,
please subscribe
so that
you get the information about all the uploaded videos first, as
you click on the insurance icon,
you have to come to mode and hot party,
which you will see below, I am
showing you by removing it, as soon as you
click on the third party icon, you will get an option
here, the search bar will appear
right there, if you subscribe,
you have to click here,
as soon as you click,
your ICC rules page will open
and from here, check the bill carefully,
if you have to do first party policy  Wheeler
car private car good option, then you are
clicking on this line, otherwise you have to do third
party, you will click on this site here, at
that time you have to wait a little,
now when we click here, then as soon as
you click on get good, a
new popup window will open for you,
wait a little and
here you have to enter the registration number i.e. your
vehicle number, its son you have to
click on Twitter, like after dialing your vehicle
number, you will click on get started details,
you will get all the details and thing number,
vehicle, garlic, model, everything of yours, it will be
searched here, finally I will
show you by entering a vehicle number,
like when you click on get etc, as you
see, all the thing details have been automatically filled,
here I have filled all my details,
which model is it, what is it,
you do not need to do anything in it,
politics start has also come, simply
you have to download it from here below,
as soon as you do it, you
need to follow this area, click on people here,
otherwise you have to click on get, as if
you click on gift cute, your
amount will be filled here, so minimum
784  Now you can do it, if you click
no here then a little value will be deceptive
but your amount increases from 16 thousand, that is, it does
not depend on how much you will get in Cheers,
then there will be no difference, so try
that your servant members will increase ₹ 15 in such a way
where you will not have to and after
putting it here you have to click on the prostrate button, you have
got your trophy, in
this way you will preside over the restraint, you will
model and absolutely everything has come, you have seen this,
click on the profit wing,
as soon as it clicks on profit, village
Cheerwa
subscribe, the match is happening, that is
how much you have to subscribe and here there is
no need to enter the date off here, subscribe your pin
code,
click on the subscribe button, if you
click on the proposal then you have to
subscribe exactly
like the paper is, the proposal number has come, even
after this some details you have to
see the entire summary, you can see your entire summary by clicking on B,
subscribe to Yuva Sangh,
it was recharged, you have to subscribe,
you have to enter your password here,
click on the subscribe button,
he has to enter his wallet pin
here  But you have to click on the top, as if you have
subscribed by clicking on the page,
now in a few seconds the last point key will be generated,
as if you have
subscribed here and here the policy
number,
click on the subscribe button, now
your policy has been downloaded, if
you want to see it, you can open it from here, right now the
downloading is going on in pending, it has
reached, now we will open it,
your policy will look something like this in Tamil, I hope
you have understood this video,
that is why we should
subscribe, you will find it on this side,
exactly here you
can fill in all your details by making a good appointment, so this was it, in this
way you
can subscribe,
subscribe
and you can ask for such videos by commenting.